<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gaming on Your Favourite Blog</title><link>https://yourfavourite.blog/tags/gaming/</link><description>Recent content in gaming on Your Favourite Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 17:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yourfavourite.blog/tags/gaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Monster Hunter: Rise - April 4</title><link>https://yourfavourite.blog/logs/2021-04-05-monster-hunter-rise-april-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yourfavourite.blog/logs/2021-04-05-monster-hunter-rise-april-4/</guid><description>Achievements Reached HR3 in Kamura Hunted Arzuros, Great Izuchi. Spent some time on an expedition to the Ruins. Crafted gear for my Buddies. Played with 3 random people for the first time, the matchmaking is really cool. TIL Learned how to use Wirebugs to fly around the map. Learned how to train Buddies Learned how to properly use the Detailed Map. Learned how to see Weapon Controls Learned how to use the Dual Blades and Sword &amp;amp; Shield Evidence</description></item><item><title>Fortnite - April 2</title><link>https://yourfavourite.blog/logs/2021-04-03-fortnite-april-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 22:44:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yourfavourite.blog/logs/2021-04-03-fortnite-april-2/</guid><description>Fortnite, I know&amp;hellip;
Achievements Won my first solo match! It was also my 2nd-ever match, so my ego has been boosted. Reached lv. 6 Played with my niece, had lots of fun :) TIL I like using the bow and arrow. Crafting is weird in this game, I need to improve. There are NPCs now? Also quests? Fortnite also has a single-player PvE mode, might be worth checking it out.</description></item><item><title>Elite Dangerous - April 1</title><link>https://yourfavourite.blog/logs/2021-04-02-elite-dangerous-april-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 21:30:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yourfavourite.blog/logs/2021-04-02-elite-dangerous-april-1/</guid><description>Achievements Reached Cadet with the Federation (ew) Grinding in the Ceos/Sothis systems. Improved my interdiction-evading skills Outfitted my ASP Explorer with 112 cargo space for questing. Goals I want to unlock the Sol system. Set up a home base. Prepare travel to Colonia. Outfit ship for exploration. Fully engineer my FSD for extended range. Unlock Guardian FSD extender for 10.5YL extra jump range.</description></item><item><title>Elite Dangerous - March 27/28</title><link>https://yourfavourite.blog/logs/2021-03-28-elite-dangerous-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 13:50:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yourfavourite.blog/logs/2021-03-28-elite-dangerous-1/</guid><description>Notable achievements Started this log! Unlocked Engineer Reached Trailblazer Purchased Asp Explorer Engineered Sensors Learned how to use the FSS (Joy 7 + Joy 2) Earned some cash. (around 10M) Reached Pathfinder! All nighter :) Reached Betancourt Base! Apparently, it&amp;rsquo;s a special station. Learned how to play the SRV Goals Set up a home base (Jameson, Surface one, Colonia) Reach Elite in Exploration to unlock Jameson Obtain materials for engineering (FSD Range) Explore the galaxy</description></item></channel></rss>